volition.com 2016-11-04

# Volition® LLC PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT

|     |  This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to this Site, www.volition.com which is owned by Volition.com LLC. By using this Site, you are agreeing to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, "Personal Information" means any information by which you can be personally identified, and includes your name, your address, your telephone number, your e-mail address and the like. Some Site pages may request Personal Information in order to help Volition.com serve you more effectively. Volition.com collects Personal Information only when you voluntarily submit such Personal Information to us, such as when placing a product order or subscribing.

For each visitor to the Site, our web servers automatically recognize information regarding the visitor's domain name (or that of the visitor's access provider). Regardless of the purpose for which it is submitted, it is Volition.com's policy to maintain all Personal Information as confidential, and to use such Personal Information only for the following purposes:

  * for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered (for example, to complete a product purchase, send a newsletter, etc.); 
  * to improve the content, appearance and utility of the Site; 
  * to track our visitors' use of the Site for internal market research; and 
  * to notify our visitors of updates to the Site. 

It is Volition.com's policy to keep Personal Information only for so long as needed for such purposes. At any time, you may obtain a summary of the Personal Information on record with Volition.com which has been collected about you via this Site. Except for Personal Information we need to complete your purchase of products, you may request at any time that Volition.com dispose of any or all Personal Information about you. In addition, at any time you may request: (i) that Volition.com correct any such Personal Information; or (ii) [that such Personal Information not be provided to third parties; or (iii)] that such Personal Information be removed from Volition.com's marketing databases. To make any request described above, send an e-mail to [privacy@volition.com](mailto:privacy@volition.com). When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Volition.com reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will mean that you accept those changes.

Of course, if you know Ray Sola and his attitudes about the Internet and Marketing, you would not have had to read this. You would know that he has been on the Internet since 1995 and works against any company that he feels is doing anything inappropriate.
